[Music]
So, the way we are
getting updates on the market, we will
try to continue the same and
our market experts Varun
and Joshi Sir are associated with us.  Varun Sir, you are
most welcome on Money.
Yes, thank you so much.  Good afternoon to all our
viewers, to you and your team.  Yes Varun Sir, I would
like to understand from you that today
is the last day of the trading week and the market is
trading with a decline.
But the way we have been
observing the market since morning, Sir, a
good recovery is visible even from the lower levels.
If we talk about the low
of Nifty, then the
market is trying to give a slight rebound from the low of 25783
and tried to come around 25850
but from there it seems that a slight
correction is coming again
and Nifty is currently trading around 25826.  If we
talk about Bank Nifty, it is
trading around 5777.  There is a drop of 300 points.
Condolences are taken forward but first of all I would
like to take your opening remarks.
Sir, how do you feel about today's market and what are you seeing
on the charts?
Yes, if you see, the market had given a breakout
above 25350 and from there we got a one way rally
around 26100, so when we were
showing 26100 yesterday also, then also we had told that there seems to be a little
stretch and there will be a little
wait and watch situation here because it is a
breakout, it does not mean that there will be selling now,
but there can be a retest from here, which is
our intraday moving averages, you will
see that 24 EMA or 10 EMA
works as a momentum indicator in the market, so the
market is coming there and
consolidating, so this is a healthy
correction and if you see from here, then the market is
not reversing from here yet, we will
wait and watch a little, I feel
that the
market can bounce back from 25650 25800 which is a zone
and the new high
which we had just hit, the recent 52 week high,
we can retest there again.
Along with this, you will see that on Nifty Bank also,
from the level of around 58,600, there has been a
little profit booking from the upper levels
and if you see there, a big
rally was seen in Bank Nifty also, so a
little profit was made from there also.
57500 to 57350 would be a very good
zone to enter again.  So a good
healthy correction is going on there as well.  So I feel that the
market had a
one-way rally somewhere.  There is an impulse
and corrective cycle going on in the market, the
cycle is in a correction there and if
someone misses the rally at a lower level then there can be an
opportunity for a better entry
in the coming time.  Yes, now we have
a special request for all the viewers who are connected with us right now, that if
you have any question related to FAO,
regarding any script or any futures,
if you want to trade FAO
futures call put, if you have any
question in your mind, then please our
comment section is open.
Please write your questions in our comment section.
I will try to get Varun Sir to
answer your question.
But meanwhile Sir Rakesh ji has
joined us Vrinda Sir and his question is
that Sir Nifty is calling for 26,000 on 4th November.
Bought at 152.  What is your view?
Please tell me the stop loss and target.
Yes, Abhish ji, if you look at it that way, our
view is not whether you buy a naked call or a put.
Still, if the viewer has a
position, then you will see that there is
a zone of around 24850800.  If you see there, if we
get a good bounce from here then we can
see a level of 26000 again.  If
we close below 24800, then
from there a further downside of 250 to 200 points
can open and if you look closely for options then it can be a
loss making trade
because then their viewer's
call of 26000 will become very big out of the money
and from there the time tick
can give a huge loss, so you should maintain a stop loss
of 24800
on the spot chart and as soon as 24800, sorry
25800, closes below it, then you should
close your position once and
enter when the market reverses.  Till the
strike price of the lower levels is reached,
I think we should maintain
a stop loss of Rs 24,800.
Yes Sir, you have rightly said that the way
uncertainties are being seen in the market,
people should
not keep their positions narrow.  It
should be kept hedged.  But Sir, there are some global
factors which I would like to discuss with you.
The way it is being said that
talks can take place between America and China.  Then the
market of discussion regarding India US trade deal is also
hot.  Sir, how do you see that the
global factors will
decide the condition and direction of the market now?
Yes Vishal ji, see 24 hours big time
in the current scenario because Trump sir has come
and Trump sir brings a lot of changes in 24 hours,
so a close
eye should be kept here and as soon as you see, on the
second day after trading, on New Year's
Day, Trump sir had tweeted and
he had given
a positive statement on the India trade deal, from there we got
a gap up of 400 points and
everyone's New Year's day was also very good.   If
you look at China as well, as
soon as their 90-day agreement of 3 months was over, they
started playing their big call back and
you will see that hopefully a meeting can take place here on 1st November, but the
statements coming from
China, from the Chinese government or from the US
side or the developments taking place on Russia,
I feel that somewhere
in the near term, whatever trade
problem is there, Trump himself is trying to solve it
because in the US too, there is a big
protest going on against him and he is also facing it
because his
MPs or the government there are also putting
pressure there, which can
increase inflation there too due to the trade deal, so if
you see somewhere,
they have made the matter quite
complicated and here they will
also have to call a session, so I
feel that hopefully, the meeting on 1st November will be with
him.  It was better and was
also good for the world market.  So from here
we have a little uncertainty, that should go away
and from here
we can gradually work on the long side in a good trade.
Sir, which sectors are you keeping on your radar right now
?
Now see, since Trump sir, our view is that in power,
we have
reduced our exposure to globally exposed companies and on domestic
focused companies like affordable housing finance,
autos, we have had a bullish view, in the
same way the market has worked till now,
now we are becoming a little positive, if we
look at IT, there is
no negative surprise, the results have also
come good and there is no negative surprise here as per the
market's expectation
and if we look at yesterday's session, then
ID had done a very good job.  Banking
stocks are also doing well.
When the PSU index, that is, the PSU banking index, was giving a breakout, we were the first to
catch the breakout here.  So
we are bullish on PSU banks as well, the
India focus is still based on Indian consumption.
You should remain bullish on those companies.
Global facing sectors like pharma or
IT, headminders come in somewhere or the other
because some or the other
statement about tariff comes in, but if you see,
valuation wise IT is looking quite good
and if someone wants to go for long term, then
you can invest in IT as well,
but the focus there will be on AI driven
stocks like assistants, coffers,
you should have a bullish view there,
not our old IT, there is a
bit of problem going on there right now
and after seeing their development here,
we will move towards the large cap ID.
Yes sir, meanwhile please also take a look at the shares of Vodafone Idea.
Sir, that stock has fallen very sharply.
Ah, it is being said that
currently there is
uncertainty, instability and decline in the company's shares.  The
reason is that the AGR
dues case, the Adjusted Gross
Revenue case, is pending in the court
and its hearing is going to take place around 27th October.
Sir, the
huge demand of DOT of Rs 9450 crore is
also a matter.  So sir, how is Vodafone Idea
looking on the charts?
Well, if you see, Vodafone had become a penny
stock.  But if you see, there was
a good consolidation in the zone of 6, 86 around six to 8
and there
a breakout has been given around 8.40, 8.45 and
in the daily charts when it went negative, it was
below 200 SMA, now it has come above 200 SMA
and here the moving averages which are
short term like 24 or 52 EMA which we
track are quite good for bullish momentum,
see the crossover here,
a golden crossover is happening here
in our daily, so I feel that
if someone has a position somewhere.  Although I
recommend avoiding FAO or
option side but if someone has created a position here in cash then
maintain a stop loss of 8.40.
In the coming days, it seems that
we may get confirmation of a double bottom or triple bottom from here on the weekly chart as well
and targets ranging from around ₹10.50 to ₹1 can be
seen here.  It is a very bullish
chart and maintain a stop loss
and if possible avoid taking positions in FAO or options.
Okay Sir, the second
stock is Federal Bank, news is coming in
that there has been a big entry of Black
Stone, you must be aware Sir that
Black Stone, the American private equity giant, has been given approval to issue convertible warrants worth ₹6200 crores
and after this news,
see, the share of the bank had
gone up by around 1.6% to the level of ₹232
and it is still witnessing a rise at the moment.
Sir, what would be your advice on Federal Bank?
How does it look on the charts?
See Vishal ji, Federal Bank is a very
strong bank, its management also does
a very strong job and here it is a
low beta stock.  But you will see that
recently there has been a huge move.
We have seen a run up from around 195 levels to 230 levels.
Even after the results, there is a lot of
momentum here.  The daily charts are a bit
stretched.  From your 10 EMA to your 24 EMA.
So there could be a slight pullback here.
Would be a good opportunity to end again.
And if you see here, there was
a range from 170 to 25.  There was a huge range.   The
stock has completed a complete consolidation zone of about one and a half years here.
And a good breakout has been achieved
and closing has also been achieved on the weekly chart.
Any pullback comes up to 25.  There will be
entry opportunity here.  A
stop loss of Rs 21,208 needs to be maintained.  Because if you
see, if you see a pattern of the bank here, then
after giving a breakout, it goes into the sideways zone.  If
you want to play momentum, if there is any decline then you can do
buy on deep strategy here.
Maintain stop loss of 208 till 25th.  It
seems that there is a big breakout here in the coming days.
Targets ranging from around 245 to 260 can also be made.
OK sir.  Gaurav Tiwari ji has joined us.
Sir, his question is that there is a
call of ₹1760 on Prestige State.  He has bought it at the price of ₹71.  This
is a call for the November series, sir.  I am asking Sir, please guide me.   If
you look at G Prestige, there
is a resistance around 1760 and the
stock is trading here only.  So
closing will be very important today.
We have got very good momentum from the lower levels.
Double bottom is confirmed from around 1500 level,
above 1670 and there is a
resistance around 1770 to 1800.
If the stock is successful
in crossing its resistance, then a
very good pattern is developing here.  If
you look at the weekly charts also, there is a cup and
handle like pattern and a target of around 1900 can be
made.
Gaurav ji has taken the position in your option.  Gaurav ji
is one of our Direct Devil traders and here his
positions are quite risky but
you can say that he has a lot of importance
in creating his positions.  So just be yourself.
Maintain today's intraday stop loss at Rs 1730.  If the
stock closes below 173 or 1730, then
exit immediately because the
expiry is very near and the time dike can be
very big, so it is
absolutely necessary to take a stop loss here.
Ok sir next stock is Paytm
call of ₹1300.  He has bought it at the price of ₹62.
This is also a call from the November series, sir.
What would be your advice on this, sir?
Which stock?
Call from Paytm 1300.  ₹62 Purchase November
Series Sir.
You can see the chart of Paytm, Vishal ji, it
is a very good chart and we got a breakout
from around 150-50 zone and after doing
a complete retest there, the stock is
currently trading at its 52 week high.  So
in yesterday's session also you will see that we got a very good
move around 139 and here it is
a normal pullback.  I
feel there is a very good structure here and it is
on its breakout.
Targets can be made around 1350 to 1400.  1355
sorry, have to maintain a stop loss of 1255.  With a
stop loss of 1255,
I feel that a target of 1400 can be achieved
in the coming days.
OK sir.  We have a next viewer with us.
He has written Sir that booked 55 point
loss in Lambar October future.  Sir, was this a
fake breakout?  Was it an OTM call or did
they eat the premium?  This
is their question.  Sir is asking about Lambar October
future?
Yes, when there was a big move in ICICI GI,
we had a view that the stock here is
known to give a lot of fake breakouts
and here we were asked to
maintain a stop loss of 1990,
I remember one of our viewers, he had a
query and here you had to maintain a stop loss
because if you
see, there has been a huge fall below 1990 here
and the
level can also reach around 1940.  So see here, there was a
fake breakout and you had
created a naked position in the future, there also our
view was that you should not create a naked position,
in futures you will have to hatch somewhere in the future
because you will see that there are
huge adjustments in the future and here
your naked position
can give huge losses, but you have placed a stop loss, it is
very good, so a good entry for you can be made in the zone of 1925 1940
and from
there we can see the levels from 1980 to 2000,
so wait till there,
if you get an entry opportunity then
you can enter back.
Sir Deepesh ji has joined us.
His question is that Sir, yesterday I bought 10 lots of Sussex Hero 3 PM
84,900 put at 40 and
sold it at 255.  What is the current view on Nifty
in the second half?  Geopolitical
intentions are also there now.  There is a lot to learn from your show.
Thank you Deepesh ji.
Thank you Mr Deepesh.  And Deepesh ji
wants to go for our Hero call and trades very well.
Deepesh ji, if you see, the
market has given a good pullback
of about 200-250 points and from here there is a healthy
correction.  24 It is absolutely necessary for you to maintain a stop loss of 25800
intraday.
From there you can buy on deep.  But the
level of 25650 can open further from here.  So
if the market moves below 25800 then
we can see levels up to 25650.
So here you should maintain stop loss once.
If you have any intraday position then it is
of 25800 and if there is a bounce from here then
we can see the level of 26,000 again.
So if the market is currently
in a consolidation zone or sideways zone then
you will have to take a stop loss.
OK sir.  Harsh Patel sir has joined us
and his question is
about the future of Kolpal, sir,
what will be the target for next month, sir?
Yes Vishal ji, the earnings of Kolpal came yesterday
and the earnings were as expected
but there was some muted growth here and the
market had factored in some surprise here
because there was a little
run up before the results, that entire run up of about 4 to 5% in the stock has gone away
and if you
see, there is a very negative structure.
Still the stock
is moving in a down trending move from the level of 1300 and the
stock has taken a good support around 2200.
Now if we get a breakout of 2200
on the downside, then the target can be around 2150 to
2050.  So, it would be best to
avoid entering any long position here.  If you want to
see any long position, then
you should enter only if the stock closes above 2350
because from there you will get a double bottom
confirmation and a good thing, a
positive thing here is that our
Polpal 20 is consolidating here at 200 SM of our weekly,
if there is a
breakdown here then you will see that there is a huge
downside risk and of 5%, so
wait for an entry at 2350, we get a
closing above 2350, we will get a double bottom
confirmation but there
can be a reversal in the stock, till then there is a down
trend and fresh entry should be avoided for now.
OK Sir Tasleem Arif ji has joined us
Sir, he has questions on two stocks.   The
first one is TCS IT stock, they have a call of ₹3100,
sir is asking for it at the price of ₹75, sir please
tell me its stop loss and target.   Yes,
generally see Vishal ji, when the expiry is near then the
price of O
seems quite attractive to you and many of our
traders viewers enter but
here you see this ₹7 is also your time dick
because it is the time value only, so you will have to
maintain a stop loss of 3060
but by 3060 your option can fall by almost 50%,
so you should definitely take a hedge
position because if you
sell a little premium in front of the premium you have paid then your
stop loss will be fixed and if there is a rally from here then
you can
also get a good profit.  So you can do call
spread or if you have a bullish view
then do call spread, there will be a better
opportunity that you can buy future and
sell call, then a hedge will be
created there.  If you see here,
TCS has given a good breakout above 3060.
It is possible that
targets ranging from 3120 to 3150 may be made in the coming days.  Quite
good is a double bottom confirmation.  A higher high has
also been formed on the daily charts and the stock can continue its upmove from here.
By maintaining the stop loss at 3060,
we can see levels up to 3150 in the coming days.   Yes
sir.  Now Sir, news is also coming about Vedta, the stock which is called the king of dividend,
Sir, and there
is also a question related to this from Tasleem ji, his question is that
he has a call of 510 at the price of ₹35, Sir,
he wants to know the stop loss and target for this also.  There were
also reports about Vedta,
sir.
Yes, you will see that in the aluminium stocks also, there
is a big mouth in the international market in tomorrow's session and Vedta has a small
part in it and a lot of corporate actions also keep happening here
in Vedta.  So
Vedta has given a good breakout
above 485 but it is important to maintain the stop loss of today's low of 487.
We saw a level of around 501 here
in intraday.  There has been a slight pullback from there
but there is a breakout and when
you look at metals now, especially on num and copper, there is
a bullish view
in the market.  It is possible that
you may see good levels here in the coming days.
But you should understand that
if someone has a call of Rs 510 with current expiry, then that is the time
value and you still have only two days left.  If
you look at today, half of the day
is over and on Monday and Tuesday you will have to be
very careful and you will have to
maintain a stop loss because the
time loss can be quite big.
Okay sir, Ravi ji has joined us sir
and his question is on BEL.  Ah his question is
that there is a 435 call.  He has said goodbye to it.  There
is October series at 90 paise.  What should be done sir?  90 paise sir, the entire
premium is gone sir.   Yes yes,
definitely we will see here Vishal ji, the
breakout here is good.  The stock is
in very good momentum.  There was consolidation from around 415
to 385 levels
and a breakout is being seen from around 415.  The
stock is trading around 422.  The
stock may show the level of 435
in the coming days.  But if you see, the
premium that they have paid or the
call purchase that they have made that went so far out of the money, it is
very difficult for it to be in the money
in two days because it is a slightly loose stock,
but if you see, it is a very good
structure and if you want to accumulate in cash then stay
here with a stop loss of 385,
in the coming days targets of 450 to 500 can be
made here in BA because you will
see, it is a very good structure and the
stock has given a good breakout here.
Okay Sir, Uttam Bera ji has joined us
Sir and his question is that there is a call of 7500 on Navama and there is a
buy of 53, he is asking what to do
Sir, please tell me, we will
check on Nova, Vishal ji, the
stock is very volatile here, we got the level of around 5600
and from there the
stock moved in a one way and got the level of around 7200 here.  If
you look closely, there
is a resistance around 7300 and
a support around 7000.  So you will see where a
middle of the range stock is moving right now and
is in a nice consolidation zone.  As soon as the
stock crosses the 7300 zone, you should
understand that a very good momentum can be created here
and levels ranging from 7500 to 7700 can
also be formed here.  The stock
is quite good.  If you have any position,
maintain a stop loss of Rs 7000.  The
stock may show good momentum in the coming days.
Levels ranging from around 7500 to 7700 can also be seen here.
Ok sir let's discuss the next stock
sir.  Next stock is our viewer's
job on the head.  Ratnakar ji is associated with us.  The
job is for ₹1420 call
of October series.  Although he has
not told the price, sir.  What do you
advise me to do, sir?
Yes Vishal ji, you see Infoz
is a stock stuck in a range because you will see that
after the corporate action,
after the liquidity increased here, the
stock is moving in a sideways zone.   It is trading
around 1280 to 1350 zone and is
continuously taking a rejection from its 200 SMA.
This time also you will see that the stock has got a rejection
from the zone of around 1420 which is 200 SM.
But if
you look at the stock here, the momentum
indicators are turning bullish.
And trying to give a range breakout from here.
As soon as the stock manages to give its close above 200 such as
1420 or a complete zone above 1420.
So in the coming days we
can see very good levels here.  Currently it
is in a range.  If you have any
long position.  You have to maintain a stop loss of 1280.
If you want to enter fresh then
wait for a level of 1420 or
gives closing above 200 SNA.  Then the stock will
get a good momentum.  Till then there
is a sideways zone.  So even today you have
received 200 rejection SMS.  The stock may
move back into your range.  So if you
buy at the support level close to the range, it will be
good risk and as soon as
you get momentum, you will get a breakout from here and the
level of around 1500 can also be seen here.
Yes, now Varun Sir would like to get information from you on the market.
See, if we look at the current price
of Nifi, it is now trading around Rs 25,860.
Ah
Nifi is seen crossing the level of 850.  Sir, if
a viewer wants to trade in Nifi right now, then
which side would be
better for him to trade?
Vishal ji, we will have to definitely go on the long side
because see, as we
will see in the beginning of the show,
we have got a movement of about 40-50 points from 25820 here
and the
market has started moving above our daily VVP of 25850.
So the pullback that we had expected has
come, the pullback is coming from the 24 EMA of the hourly
itself and the market is
also crossing the high of the previous hour of the hourly, it is
possible that
we may get a good momentum from here, so
maintain a stop loss of 25800, we
can go on the long side only because there is
a good momentum in the market, there was an intraday pullback
and you are getting a good entry opportunity,
so it will be better to enter from here and
play on the long side only
and what about Sir Bank Nifty, a
good recovery is being seen in Bank Nifty also, it is
trading around 57890.  The
decline of 300 points has now reduced
to only 185 points.
Yes, you see, Bank Nifty was a big
outperformer in the market and here
I feel that it can do a little more consolidation.
But 58000 5850
can play a resistance because you will see that is where the
market gave a breakdown so that could be
a retest.  From 57500 to
57350 would be a
good opportunity to enter.  Here
I feel that the risk level is not that favourable, so it would be
better to enter when Bank Nifty falls a little more.
If someone has a long position and wants to
hold it, then
maintain a stop loss of Rs 57,800 on a closing basis.  If
it breaks, it would be better to exit once and
enter at a lower level.  But here
Vishal ji, it will be important for our viewers to
understand each and every thing.  There is no entry here.
It does not mean that you have to sell here.
You have to do better level weight.
As soon as the breakout occurs, you have to play on the upside
because there is a huge momentum and
any wrong entry here
can give you a huge loss.  So it would be
better if you take the trade only after waiting and watching.
Okay Sir, apart from some FAO stocks, I would
like to discuss other scripts also with you because our
viewers are continuously asking you questions.  Sir
Ravi Kumar's question is on Magellanic Cloud,
do you track this stock sir?
He has 700 shares at a price of ₹88.
And I am asking what to do?
Yes, Sir,
we do not have any coverage on our magnetic cloud, it would be better if
I avoid commenting.
Okay Okay Okay Sir can you comment on Hitachi Energy
Sir.  Niradri ji is associated with us
and he has asked a question, Sir, there are 60
shares of Power India which is
known as Hitachi Energy, Sir.  And the
buying price is Rs 21,600.  Should I hold for
25000? The level of 25000 can come, sir? The
holding period, sir, is asking for a maximum of
two years. Sir
Vishal ji, you will see that the stock had a good run-
up and if you look at our monthly and weekly
charts, there was a lot of stretch, from
around the level of 22000 up to be very pricey around the level of 21800 and
from there, by making a rounding top in the daily chart, the
stock has declined here, there was a
breakout breakdown, it was around 18500,
now it is declining from there and the
good thing for the viewer is that the stock is
approaching its 200 SM,
around 16200. If you want to accumulate back, you have to
add some to your portfolio because you
will see that the structure on the monthly and weekly charts
is quite good, the structure on the daily chart had
deteriorated a bit, but it is
coming around 200, so one would be a better
opportunity painter, so you  You
can enter around 16200 with a stop loss of 15500
and if the stock gives a reversal from here, then
you can see the levels around 18500 and if it sustains then you can
also get the levels of 21,000-22,000.
But here you are getting a better
opportunity to enter.
If your view is quite bullish then
you should enter around 16,200.  You can
take a bat there for a long term.
Sir Neha Singh ji has joined us.
Varun Sir, his question is on SCI, Shipping
Corporation of India.  She is asking Sir, please
tell me something about this also.
Our Vishal ji had a very bullish view on Shipping Corporation and if
you see, our model
portfolio, Golfi, which we are small case
managers, we have included it in our model portfolio here.  There was
a consolidation zone from around 25 to 238 and
we got a very good breakout in yesterday's session
and that momentum is continuing today also.
So, from here,
after a very good consolidation from a very good chart, the
stock has got momentum here.
Targets of around 300 to 350 can be
made here in the coming days.  If anyone falls here, there
is definitely a buying opportunity around 240 245 and the
stock has given a very good breakout from here.
Okay Sir, if we talk about today's market fall, then the sectors that are getting
hit the most are FMCG,
Banking and Pharma.  Sir, should you still keep these
three sectors in the avoid list
or are you getting any opportunity today
on the screens?
See, if you look at Vishal G Pharma,
in selective pockets, like two days
ago we captured a breakout of SPL and
we got a move of around 4 to 5%,
we also got very good momentum in Divi's Lab, so in
selected stocks,
you are getting opportunity in Pharma,
so you will have to go stock specific, in the same way, if
you look at it in a similar way, it is the
same in FMCG also, it is moving in a range,
like if you look at HUL, it
is in a very range-bound down trend, but if
you look at Britannia or
Mary, they are in very good momentum.
So you have to go stock specific
because you will go in a broader way so here
I feel you may get stuck.  So if
you trade by finding the stock specific levels, then there
is a better opportunity there.  So as a sector
wise there is no bullish momentum here.
But here
I would not advise you to avoid the sector at all.  But you will have to
catch the momentum by researching stocks from the same sector.
So there is a better opportunity for
entry and good trades are also being made there.
Okay sir, today many big companies will
also release their September quarter results, the
list of which I am telling you.
After that I will ask you questions.  Like today the
results of Dr Reddy's Laboratories will
come, SBI Cards & Payment Services,
SBI Life Insurance Company, Cofraz,
ITC Hotels, Supreme Petro, Camp,
Brigade Hotel Ventures, Sigachi Industries,
Jinak Kushal Industries, NDL Ventures and
eClerk Services. Sir,
if someone wants to keep all these stocks in their portfolio from a trading point of view, then should they
keep them or avoid them? Perform only after the results are out.
Absolutely, Vishal ji, if you have a
long term view, then one of the
quarters or quarterly results do
not make much difference. And as you mentioned about
Dr Reddy's Cofraz, here the
stocks are moving in a range bound momentum and
we are not seeing a breakout from here.
But if you see, there is a very good
structure and very good companies. If you have a
long term view, then
you have to stay here. If suddenly some bad
management commentary comes or the results are
very bad, then you will see that the
next quarter will also be bad, then you have to take a
decision here. Rest of the
stocks are good and the company management here is also
very good. So, absolutely here you have to  The
position should be maintained.  If
you have a short term position, that is, you have to do
some work intraday or you have a very
short term position, then I advise you
that it is better not to create any position before the event.
Because the volatility increases
significantly before and after the event
and if our
traders are unable to manage the risk, they incur
huge losses.  So that's why
I'm talking about avoiding it.  But
if you have any position for the long term, you should
definitely hold it.
Ok Varun sir, thank you very much.  You
took away valuable time.  You have
openly expressed your views on various stocks and tried to provide a
very educational and
financial retreat to our viewers.   Before
leaving, sir, if you have any disclaimer,
please do give it.
Vishal ji, whatever stocks we
discussed today are not my personal portion.  The
company may be part of the company's model
portfolio.  Being a
small case manager may be stocks in our quite model
portfolio.
Securities markets are subject to
market.  So, whatever trade you do, you should trade only after
consulting your financial advisor,
knowing the stop loss and the risk
and past performance does not guarantee
any future outlook, so keep that in mind.
ok thank you so much sir.   Thank
you.
So, stay with us for all the latest news related to the country, world and business world
and keep watching Money.
[music]